Guide to the Oversize Manuscripts Collection 1648-2018 MS OS
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Oversize Manuscripts From Other Collections, 1714-2018
  - [Y-Astor Family Papers], 1790-1877 (Oversize small, medium, large)
    See Astor Family Papers finding aid for further information on oversize manuscripts from this collection.
  - [Y-Banyar Family Papers] (Oversize small, medium, large)
    Other Finding Aids Note
    See Goldsboro Banyar and Banyar Family Papers finding aid for further information on oversize materials from this collection.
  - [Y-Belknap, Waldron Papers] Documents, 1816-1843 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Belknap, Waldron Papers] Print of Government House, 1902 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Bernheimer, Charles L. Papers, MS 58], 1916-1936 (Oversize medium)
    Oversize items from the Charles L. Bernheimer papers, MS 58. See the finding aid for that collection for content description.
  - [Y-Bible and Fruit Mission Society, MS 59], 1877, 1900, 1950 (Oversize small)
    3 items removed from Society records. See MS 59 finding aid
  - [Y-Bowers Family Papers], 1748-1777 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Bowers Family Papers] Genealogy Materials, 1944, Undated (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Bowers Family Papers] Leases, 1714-1789 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Bowers Family Papers] Diagrams and Maps, 17911816, undated (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Bradish, Luther. Papers, MS 71] Various documents (2 folders), 1800s (Oversize medium)
    2 folders of oversize documents from the Bradish papers, MS 71; see the Bradish finding aid for details.
  - [Y-Brown Brothers Harriman] 100th Anniversary Dinner Seating Plan, 1925 December 18 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Brown Brothers Harriman] Group Portrait, US/UK Conference; Exterior Photos BBH Building, 1941, c.1960 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Brown Brothers Harriman] Headstone Plans- Greenwood Cemetery, 1939 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Brown Brothers Harriman] James Crosby Brown Estate, 1934 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Brown Brothers Harriman] Mary Brown's Estate, Will, Maps, 1922-1927 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Brown Brothers Harriman] National City Bank Building Plans, 1929 January (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Brown Brothers Harriman] New Wall Street Building: Delano Correspondence- Plans, 1923-1926 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Brown Brothers Harriman] W. Averill Harriman- Chicago Sun Tribune: 21st Birthday Feature, 1911 April 27 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Browne Family Papers] Deeds, 1751-1802 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Caledonian Club] Photographs (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Canon-Cannon-Canoune] Correspondence, 1906-1909 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Canon-Cannon-Canoune] Newspaper Clippings, 1932-1953 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Caro, Robert A. Archive (MS 3202)] "Annals of Politics. The Power Broker. IThe Best Bill-Drafter in Albany," New York Times, 1974 July 18 (Oversize large)
    Two-page advertising spread "From the first four articles by Robert A. Caro, about Robert Moses and the uses of political power in New York, beginning in this week's issue (July 22) of The New Yorker. Yes, The New Yorker." (29.5 x 23.5)
  - [Y-Certificates] Mechanick Society- John Cameron, 1803 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Certificates] Miscellaneous, 1795-1968 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Certificates] Miscellaneous, 1862-1967 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Certificates] Miscellaneous, 1872-1908 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Certificates] German Society of N.Y., 1785 October 3 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Certificates] Garibaldi Statue in Washington Square Park, 1888 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Certificates] Post, 1835-1864 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Certificates] Post, 1864-1921 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Certificates] U.S.S. Wasp / H.M.S. Frolic, 1812 December 31 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Clark, Donald F., Collection] Deeds for Kingston, NY, 1717 February 20; 1722 March 2 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Clark, Donald F., Collection] Americae Pars Meridionalis (map), circa 1650 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Coke, John A. Papers] Book Recording Circulars, 1863-1864 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Coke, John A. Papers] Endorsement Book, 1864-1865 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Coke, John A. Papers] List of Retails and Exemptions, Richmond County, 13th Congressional District, 1862 December (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Confederate States of America] Confederate Army Records, 1861-1865 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Cunningham, Bill. MS 3137], 1998-2014 (Oversize small)
    Oversize items from the Bill Cunningham collection, MS 3137. See the finding aid for that collection for content description.
  - [Y-Carole De Saram Papers (MS 3059)], 1978-2006 (Oversize small)
    See finding aid for Carole De Saram papers (MS 3059) for details on oversize content.
  - [Y-Delafield Family] Photostats, Undated (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Drive to Protect the Ladies Mile Historic District] Supporting Research, book proofs and article (4 folders) (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Duane Family Papers] Leases, Duanesburg, 1765-1797 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Duane Family Papers] Leases, Duanesburg, 1803-1837 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Duane Family Papers] Surrenders and Grants, Duanesburg, 1791-1831 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Duane Family Papers] Legal papers and notes, Duanesburg, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Duane Family Papers] Legal documents and papers, Princetown, Albany County, 1765 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Duane Family Papers] Legal documents and papers, Princetown, Albany County, 1731-1748 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Duane Family Papers] Legal documents and papers, Ulster County, 1735-1754 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Duane Family Papers] Legal documents and papers, Socialborough, 1767-1775 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Dutchess County Collection (MS 186)] Oversize items, circa 1696-1767, 1838 (Oversize large)
    These items were in a third box of the collection, but were humidified, flattened, and moved to oversize folders by conservator Katarzyna (Bator) Vargas in September 2019. See the Bobcat entry for the Dutchess County Collection (MS 186) for the entire collection.
  - [Y-Elmira 1948 Election Study (MS 196)] Maps (2 of 2) (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Erasmus Hall Records (MS 201) (folder 1 of 3)] Long photographs of the complete faculty, 1912 (Oversize large)
    Taken on campus at time of 125th anniversary celebration.
    Folder 1.1 (numbered copy 1): Formerly framed (frame discarded 2021), with only accurate identification of faculty member.
    Folder 1.2 (numbered copy 2): This numbered copy was presented in Dec. 1972 by Ms. Alex Cameron, a teacher who appears in the photo. Poor condition (split in half).
    Folder 1.3 (flat copies): Three copies (one complete, two partial).
    See Guide to the Erasmus Hall Records, 13251989 (bulk, circa 17751975), MS 201.
  - [Y-Erasmus Hall Records (MS 201) (folder 2 of 3)] Chapel window depicting scenes in the life of Erasmus, presented by the Alumni Association, June 18, 1911 (Oversize large)
    Original watercolor executed by the Church Glass and Decorating Company of New York, which served as the basis for the design of the window. 25 x 28", in a large cardboard portfolio.
  - [Y-Erasmus Hall Records (MS 201) (folder 3 of 3)] Map of the town of Flatbush, made Nov. 10, 1797 by Jeremiah Lott, 1902 (Oversize large)
    Reproduction certified as accurate by the State Engineer and Surveyor, 1902. 18 x 26". Gift of Herebert [sic] S. Wynkoop, 1912.
  - [Y-Erving-King Papers] Documents, 1804-1931, Undated (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Erving-King Papers] Geneological Charts, Undated (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Erving-King Papers] Maps, 1789-1934, Undated (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Facsimilies] Miscellaneous, Undated (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Fairchild, Charles S.] Diplomas and Photograph, 1887-1929 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Falk, Myron, Papers (MS 3047)], 1923-1944 (Oversize small)
    Scope and Contents Note
    Includes various oversize items from the Myron Falk papers. See the Falk finding aid for details.
  - [Y-Falk, Myron, Papers (MS 3047)], 1913-1930 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Four Seasons Restaurant collection (MS 3151)] Loose material from scrapbooks, circa 1970-2015, undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Four Seasons Restaurant collection (MS 3151)] Loose material from scrapbooks, 2016, undated (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Four Seasons Restaurant collection (MS 3151)] Photographs. Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-2015 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Four Seasons Restaurant collection (MS 3151)] New location. Isay Weinfeld architectural designs, 2016-2017 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Four Seasons Restaurant collection (MS 3151)] New location. HMWhite. Four Seasons North & South Terrace Preliminary Planting Palette, 2018 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Fox,Gustavus Vasa Collection] Commissions, Certificate of Appointment, and Passport, 1852-1871 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Freedman Family Papers and Other Documents (MS 231)] (1 of 2 folders), 1914 July (Oversize small)
    Verhovay Aid Society photographs (2).
    Two large mounted photographs (mounts measure 22 x 14 inches) of attendees to the convention of the Verhovay Aid Society, a Hungarian national fraternal organization, Passaic, New Jersey, July 1914. The second of the two listed below shows the group at flag raising ceremonies on Long Island on Sunday, July 26, 1914 (see Passaic Daily News, Monday, July 27, 1914, p. 13).
    A VERHOVAY KONVENCIO DELEGATUSAI PASSAICON 1914 JULIUS H-BAN BELDEGREEN FENYKEPE 52 32 AVE C N.Y. {Delegates to the Averhovay Convention, Passaic, July 1914; photographed by Beldegreen Fenykepe, 32 Avenue C, N.Y.}
    A VERHOVAY EGYLET 38 IK N.Y. FIOKJANAK ZAZLOSZENTELSI UNNE PELYE 1914 JULIUS 2GAN [26AN?] {The Averhovay Association, Branch No. 38 of New York}
    For details see Guide to the Freedman Family Papers and Other Documents, 17651968 (bulk, 19301950), MS 231.
  - [Y-Freedman Family Papers and Other Documents (MS 231)] (2 of 2 folders), undated (Oversize small)
    [Purse?]
  - [Y-Friend of City Hall Park], 1998 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Fulton, Robert Papers] Indenture with Christiana Morris for property on Reed Street, 1810 May 30 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Gates, Horatio Papers] Commission, 1775 June 19 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Gates, Horatio Papers] Pay and Rations of the U.S. Army, 1776 December 31 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Gates, Horatio Papers] Returns, 1778 July-October (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Gates, Horatio Papers] Resolutions of Harvard, 18 June 1779 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Gates, Horatio Papers] Society of Cincinnati, 1785 December 10 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Goldstone, Harmon Hendricks], 1941-1985 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Guion Family Papers (MS 3013)], 1892, 1898, Undated (Oversize medium)
    See the finding aid for the Guion family papers (MS 3013) for item content.
  - [Y-Dr. Charles Hale] Certificates, 1827-1834 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Joanna Hallett] Grace A. Wixom Diplomas, 1899-1909 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Hare Family Papers] Diplomas and Photos- Montgomery Hale, 1870-1932 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Jacob Harvey Family Papers (MS 306)], 1846-1847, 1947 (Oversize small)
    Includes Supplement to the Dublin Evening Post (26 March 1946), the Dublin Evening Post (31 July 1847), and U.S. Department of the Interior Geological Survey map of the Vanderbilt Mansion Historic Site in New York (stamped 1st Proof, June 1947).
  - [Y-Shirley Hayes Papers] Washington Square Park, undated (Oversize medium)
    Includes 2 posters related to the campaign to keep cars out of Washington Square Park.
  - [Y-Hendricks Family Papers (MS 295)] Belleville Copper Photograph, undated (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Horticultural Society of New York Records (MS 3033)], 1960s-1996 (Oversize large)
    Includes oversize items from the Hort collection: New York Flower Show and other posters, floor plans of the New York Coliseum and other plans related to the Flower Shows, and a set of plans for the Vanderlip estate.
  - [Y-Hyde, James Hazen, Papers. MS 319] (2 folders), 1917 (Oversize small, large)
    2 folders: 1 small oversize, the other large. Oversize small includes photographs and certificates. Oversize large includes a poster, in French, for event at Nantes at which Hyde spoke; this is folder 2 of 2 of material for this event. The first folder includes Hyde's remarks. See the finding aid for the Hyde papers.
  - [Y-Iselin Family Papers and Photographs. MS 3076] (1 folder), 1948, undated (Oversize large)
    Two items:
    1. "Stammtafel der / Genealogical Tree ISELIN von Basel," 1948.
    2. "Antique Milesian Famili De O'Donnell" [O'Donnell family tree], undated.
    For details, see Guide to the Iselin Family Papers and Photographs, 18801991, MS 3076.
  - [Y-Itzler Collection] Certificates, 1860-1929 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Kendrick, Henry L.], 1831-1868 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-King, Billie Jean] Oversize from MS 3147 (Oversize large)
    See Billie Jean King collection finding aid.
  - [Y-King, Rufus papers] Appointments, commissions, and other documents issued to Rufus and John Alsop King. 15 items., 1796-1825 (Oversize small)
    Contains presidential signatures, among them George Washington and John Adams.
  - [Y-Louis Kuhn] Certificates, 1875-1881 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Martha J. Lamb Papers] Art, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Martha J. Lamb Papers] Certificates, 1888-1889, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Martha J. Lamb Papers] Christmas Songs and List, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-John Laurance Papers] Appointment of John Laurance as Judge of the New York District Court, 1794 May 6 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Le Boutillier Family Papers] Artwork and Portfolio, undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Lefferts-Wetherill Family Papers] Certificates and printed material, 1848-1919 (Oversize medium)
    Folder contains mounted Civil War documents of Tennessee Union soldier Joseph B. Wetherill (including Oath of Allegiance to the United States); Samuel Wetherill's certificate of membership in the Zelosophic Society; John Wetherill's appointment as a delegate to the Antietam Battlefield Board; and several other appointments and certificates.
  - [Y-Lefferts Wetherill Family Papers] Certificate in latin issued to Samuel Wetherill, undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Lockman, DeWitt M.] Inventory (Christian) Books, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Low, Fleming, and King family papers (MS 3091)], 1861 August 17 (Oversize small)
    Commission of Cornelius Low King as First Lieutenant in the 14th Regiment of Infantry. Signed by U.S. President Abraham Lincoln and Secretary of War Simon Cameron. (Gift of Nolle King and the King Family, 2019.)
  - [Y-Luce, Henry, Papers. (MS 3014)] (10 folders), 1939-1965 (Oversize small)
    Includes various oversize items from the Henry R. Luce papers. See the Luce finding aid for details.
  - [Y-Luce, Henry, Papers. (MS 3014)] (2 folders), 1912-1913, 1941 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Luce, Henry, Papers. (MS 3014)], circa 1933-1949 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Martin Family] Certificates, 1890-1925 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McAneny Collection] Photographs, undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McBean Collection] Apple, Vauderburgh, Bickley Indenture, 1715 June 2 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McBean Collection] Gilbert Livingston Commission, 1769 August 9 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McBean Collection] Indentures, 1785 December (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-McBean Collection] Land Grant- Remsen and Brinckerhoff, signed by George Clinton, 1786 May 12 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-McBean Collection] Morris Deed, 1772 May 25 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McBean Collection] Muhlenburgh Deed, 1759 January 15 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McBean Collection] Morris Commission- Superintendant of Roads, 1799 February 26 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McComb Papers] Orders for Marble for City Hall, 1808 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Documents, 1780-1781 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Documents, 1756-1772 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Documents, 1776 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Documents, 1777 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Hospital Plans, 1782 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Inventories and Letters, 1782-1786 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Kosciuszko Drawings of West Point Forts and Returns, 1779, Undated (Oversize large)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Letters, List of Officers, Death Warrant, 1778 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Morning Reports, 1776 May (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Muster Rolls and Pay Extract, 1776 May (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Muster Rolls and Pay and Sick Reports, 1776 June (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Morning Reports, 1776 June (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Morning Reports, 1776 July-August (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Muster Rolls and Pay Reports, 1776 July (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Muster Rolls and Pay Reports, 1776 August (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Muster Rolls and Pay Reports, 1776 September (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Muster Rolls and Pay Reports, 1776 October (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Muster Rolls and Pay Reports, 1776 November (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Muster Rolls and Pay Reports, 1776 December (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Non-Importation Agreement Papers, 1770 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Report of the Barrack Guard and Monthly Return, 1775 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-McDougall Papers] Returns and Letters, 1779 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-McKesson Papers] Roll of persons taking Oath of Allegiance (Jewish names), 1741 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-McVickar Family] Diplomas and Certificates, 1865-1908 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Mitchell, Edward] Certificates, 1890 January 27 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Murra, Laura Shaw. MS 3142]. Posters, 1992-2003 (Oversize medium)
    Oversize posters from Murra collection on feminism (MS 3142); see that finding aid for item list.
  - [Y-Nathan, Edgar J, Jr. MS 438] (2 folders), 1876-1961 (Oversize small)
    See Edgar J. Nathan Papers finding aid for details of content.
  - [Y-Nathan, Edgar J, Jr. MS 438], circa 1930s-1940s (Oversize large)
    See Edgar J. Nathan, Jr. papers finding aid for details of content.
  - [Y-Naval History Society Collection/G.V. Fox] Drawings of "The Raft" (2) (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-New York State National Guard, 9th Regiment (MS 3085)], 1858, 1864, 1944-1945 (Oversize medium)
    Holds oversize items from the 9th Regiment collection (MS 3085). See that finding aid for details of content.
  - [Y-1914 Time Capsule Collection] Newspapers, 1914 May (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Ogden, David], 1811-1815 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Olds, Irving S.] Woodbury Subdivision, 1930-1940 (Oversize large)
    Contains oversize maps and blueprints about property Olds owned in Nassau County, New York. There are references to his property being involved in the construction of the Northern State Parkway.
  - [Y-Olcott, Eben. Papers] Maps of Peru and Panama, Undated (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Pelton, William Snow] Certificates, 1826-1830 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Phelps Papers] Diplomas and Correspondence, 1855-1877 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Pickhardt Papers] Photographs of Otto and others at a Russian Prisioner's of War Camp, Sagan, Germany, 1919 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Robert Price papers (MS 3130)] John V. Lindsay congressional campaign posters, 1958-1964 (Oversize large)
    ELECT / JOHN LINDSAY / [portrait] / REPUBLICAN CANDIDATE / FOR CONGRESS / VOTE ROW A [1 copy]
    VOTE FOR / GOVERNOR ROCKEFELLER'S TEAM! / FOR CONGRESS - 17TH DISTRICT / JOHN LINDSAY / FOR CONGRESS - 19TH DISTRICT / RICHARD S. ALDRICH / FOR STATE SENATOR / JOSEPH PINTO / FOR ASSEMBLYMAN / PAUL J. CURRAN / VOTE ROW "A" ALL THE WAY [1 copy]
    RE-ELECT / CONGRESSMAN JOHN V. / [portrait] / LINDSAY / OUTSTANDING PUBLIC SERVANT / VOTE ROW A [4 copies]
  - [Y-Robert Price papers (MS 3130)] John V. Lindsay mayoral campaign posters, 1965 (Oversize large)
    Dirty air. / Dirty lungs. / Dirty laundry. / He'll do / something / about air pollution/ ELECT / JOHN / LINDSAY / MAYOR / Vote the Lindsay Team / Lindsay-Mollen-Costello [1 copy, on stiff cardboard]
    "He is fresh and everyone else is tired." / VOTE FOR / JOHN LINDSAY / FOR MAYOR [full length portrait in two parts]
    Milton Mollen / FOR COMPTROLLER / [portrait] / Elect Lindsay/Mollen/Costello [1 copy]
  - [Y-Rogers Family Papers] Newspaper articles relating to the Rogers family, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Rogers Family Papers] Certificate from Massachusetts Charitable Merchants Association Awarding Silver Medal to Rogers Statutettes, 1890 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Rogers Family Papers] Bound volume 1 and copies of Country Life Magazine, 1921 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Rogers Family Papers] Accompanying letters, notes, and articles from bound volume no.1, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Rogers Family Papers] Drafts of Rogers family trees, Undated (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Ruggles, George D.], 1855-1893 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Saint Andrews Society] Membership certificates, 1889, 1926 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Scoppetta, Nicholas. Papers] Big Apple poster and Children's Aid Society award certificate, 1976, 1993 (Oversize large)
    Poster: The Big Apple / You have to be a little crazy to live in New York, but you'd be nuts to live anywhere else. April '76; inscribed "To my good friend Nick Scoppetta / With great affection and warm regards / Abe Beame."
    Award certificate: Children's Aid Society / Presented by the / Trustees / to / Nicholas Scoppetta / President / 1987-1993; with a reproduction of a historic photograph of children playing in a tenement-lined street.
  - [Y-7th Regiment Records] Series XIV: Panoramic Views, 1893-1917 (Oversize large)
    Nine photographs:
    Zurich (1893)
    7th Regiment, Peekskill Camp (1911 June)
    First Brigade NYNG Camp at Orange, Connecticut Maneuver Campaign (1912 Aug. 10-19)
    West Point Parade Ground (1914)
    McAllen, Texas (1916 Aug. 8)
    McAllen, Texas (1916 Sep. 6)
    McAllen, Texas (1916)
    Madero, Texas (1916)
    Camp Wadsworth, Spartanburg, SC (1917)
  - [Y-Scriba, Frederick and George] Certificates, 1790-1816 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Sharman, William. MS 3068] (8 items), 1916-1949 (Oversize medium)
    Photographs (3 panoramas) | McAllen, Texas |1916
    Photograph (1 print) | "Living Insignia | of the | Twenty-Seventh Division | "New York's Own" | Breakers of the Hindenburg Line. | Formed of 10,000 Officers and Enlisted Men | Major-General John R. O'Ryan, Commanding." | 1919
    Photographs (3 prints) | Manufacturers Trust, Featherbed Lane (Bronx) | 1949
    Award | Office of Price Administration | 1944
  - [Y-Shepard, Helen Miller Gould Papers] Certificates, 1859-1910 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Ships and Shipping Collection (MS 563)] (Oversize small)
    See the finding aid for the New-York Historical Society ships and shipping collection (MS 563) for item content.
  - [Y-Ships and Shipping Collection (MS 563)] (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Ship Bombay] Letters of Marque, 1810-1813 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Squier, E.G.] Sketches of Lancaster Castle, 1867 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Staten Island Papers], 1810-1899 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Stevens, Ebenezer. Papers] Commission, 1798 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Stewart, William George. MS 594]. Exports from New York to Mexico., 1841 (Oversize large)
    Oversize documents from the Stewart papers. See William George Stewart, MS 594, finding aid.
  - [Y-Stoutenburgh Family] Copies, Undated (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Stoutenburgh Family] Original Documents, 1741-1806 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Stoutenburgh Family] Family Tree (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Strong Family Papers] Deeds, 1803-1819 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Strong Family Papers] Deeds, 1790 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Strong Family Papers] Deeds, 1784-1815 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Taber, Sydney Richmond. Collection], 1786 (Oversize small)
    Includes one document titled "A brief state of facts" in re: Hardenbergh (or Hardenburgh) Patent. See Bobcat catalog for Taber collection for more information. Item found on shelf and added to catalog entry and to oversize fiding aid in September 2021.